a raffle dot once this needs to be an async function, not just a regular function.
"raffle.once" 它需要一个 `async` 函数，而不是一般函数
Let's try that one more time, get latest timestamp is the correct function.
让我们来再试一次， "getLatestTimeStamp" 才是正确的函数
So let's update this with the correct latest. Let's put latest in there.
让我们更新为正确的 "Latest"，把 "Latest" 放进去
Because I'm spelling something's wrong. I sure am
好像还有一些拼写错误，改一下
looks like we're printing out recent winner here when we haven't even initialized it.
我们在这里打印了 "recentWinner"，它此处还没有被初始化
So let's move it up. And then we'll do console dot log recent winner.
我们把这里移上去，接下来我们运行 `console.log(recentWinner)`
So I know this is a massive test here. But let's give it a try
这里已经有很多测试了，让我们来试一下
and see if everything kind of does what we think it should do.
看看它是否能按照我们所设想的那样正常运行
And it's slowing down here, which is good because we're doing a lot of stuff.
这次运行会比较慢，这很正常，因为我们要执行的东西太多了
And uh huh, we finally get this passing thing to come out.
啊哈，我们终于让所有这些测试都通过了
And we did a ton of console dot logging so so there's a lot of stuff in here
我们打印了一大堆东西，所以这里有很多内容
of the signers are getting printed out.
"signer" 的所有信息都被打印了出来
So let's just make this a little easier to read. We'll add dot address to all these,
让我们把它变得更易读一些，给它们都添上 `.address`
we can see who the winner is.
这样就可以看到优胜者是谁了
So it looks like the winner is going to be account number one,
看起来优胜者是序号为 1 的账户
which is great. So what we can do now that we know account number one is going to be the winner,
很好，现在我们就已经知道账号 1 是优胜者了
we can get that winners starting balance way down here before we call fulfill random words.
我们可以获取优胜者的初始余额，就在我们调用 "fulfillRandomWords" 之前
So we'll say const winner, starting balance equals await accounts one dot get balance,
所以我们要写 `const winnerStartingBalance = await accounts[1].getBalance()`
yes, you can just call get balance right like that.
没错，你可以像这样直接调用 "getBalance"
And now that we have the winner starting balance back in our tests,
现在我们有了优胜者的初始余额，就可以回到我们的测试中
we can say const winner, ending balance equals await ounce one dot get balance.
我们可以运行 `const winnerEndingBalance = await accounts[1].getBalance()`
And we can make sure that this winner got paid what they need.
我们要确保这个优胜者得到他应得的报酬
So now we're going to do a big assert with some money stuff, just trust me, this is what the math is.
现在我们要运行一大块关于资金的 "assert"，相信我，这就是一点数学问题
So we're going to do assert dot equal winner balance.to string,
所以我们要执行 `assert.equal(winnerBalance.toString())`
excuse me winter ending balance.to string
抱歉，应该是 `winnerEndingBalance.toString()`
should equal the winner starting balance dot add the raffle entrance fee
它应该等于 `winnerStartingBalance.add(raffleEntranceFee)`
that multiplied by the additional and trance that add the raffle entrance fee that we paid.to string.
.mul(additionalEntrants).add(raffleEntranceFee).toString()`
So this math is basically saying the winner should end with a balance of all of the money that everybody else added to this contract.
这里的意思就是，优胜者最后的余额应该等同于所有人在合约中投入的资金
And that's it. So we can run this test one more time.
就是这样，现在我们可以再运行一次测试
And Gosh, darn it, it passed.
哦，天呐，它通过了
Okay, so there was a lot of code here.
OK，这里的代码已经很多了
And this might have been one of the hardest pieces of this entire course is going to be this part right here.
整个课程最难得部分可能就是这一部分了
So if you struggled a little bit with this, don't let that bog you down.
所以如果你在这里遇到了一些困难的话，不要让它阻碍你前进的步伐
This is probably one of the more difficult sections of this course,
这应该是属于本课程里比较难的一部分了
let's do a quick refresher of just this test that we're doing.
让我们快速地回顾一下我们所做的这些测试
And then we'll see in an action when we do it. In our staging test.
随后我们将看一下 "staging" 测试中具体操作
What we did is we're picking a winner resetting the lottery and we're sending money.
我们完成了选取优胜者，重置抽奖，以及发送资金
Basically what we're doing is we're testing that this fulfill random words thing
我们基本上测试的就是这个 "fulfillRandomWords" 里的内容
does what we want it to do a random winner wins and they get the money.
我们要做的就是，随机选取以一个优胜者，然后把钱给他
So how do we actually do that?
那么我们实际上是怎么操作的呢？
Well, we first started off by having a bunch of random people enter the lottery.
首先，我们让数个随机用户进入到了抽奖中
Great. Sounds good.
很好，听起来不错
Now what we wanted to do was we want to call perform upkeep and fulfill random words,
接下来，我们要做的就是调用 "performUpkeep" 以及 "fulfillRandomWords"
we want to pretend that the random number was drawn.
我们要假装自己抽了一个随机数
And that's what this code down here does is it calls that random number
下面这段代码所做的就是调取一个随机数
but and what we could have done was we could have had all these assert and checked all the variables. After we did this,
但在我们执行所有 "assert" 以及检查所有变量之前，我们要先执行这个
right. We could have totally done that.
对吧，我们就是这么做的
However, on a test net where we don't always know exactly when a transaction is going to finish.
然而，在测试网上我们无法随时确定交易是否已经完成
We have to wait If we have to listen for an event to be fired,
我们必须等待，直到我们监听到了 "event" 的触发
before, we could call the transactions that would end this whole thing,
在我们完成交易结束这一切之前
we needed to set something up to listen for that event to be fired.
我们需要设置一些东西来监听 "event" 的触发
And we said, hey, only once this event is fired only once this transaction is called,
然后我们说的就是，嘿，只有当这个 "event" 被触发，只有当这个交易被调用的时候
can we do our testing
我们才可以执行我们的测试
now for our local network, we are mocking the VRF coordinators,
在我们的本地网络中，我们模拟了 "VRFCoordinator"
we have control, we know exactly when this is going to run.
我们有控制权，知道它运行时的确切情况
But on a test net, we don't.
但在测试网上，我们是做不到的
So you'll see in our staging tests, we won't have any of this here.
所以你将会看到，在我们的 "staging" 测试中，就没有这些东西了
And we'll have to rely on setting up a listener to listen for the channeling VRF and the keepers to fire their events.
到时我们将不得不设置一个 "listener" 来监听 "Chainlink VRF" 以及 "Keepers" 对这些 "event" 的触发
And that's why the staging test is going to be so important to make sure that we're doing everything correct.
这就是为什么 "staging" 测试如此的重要，它能确保我们所做的一切都是正确的
And that's why we set up our local tests like this,
这也是为什么我们会把本地测试设置成这样
so that it mimics what we're going to be doing on our statement test what we're going to be doing on a real network here.
这样它就能模仿我们在 "staging" 测试和真实网络中的所作所为
And again, we're setting up this listener and we're saying, Ah, once we do here, this event,
再解释一遍，我们设置的这个 "listener" 就相当于是在说，啊，一旦我们触发了这个 "event"
then we're going to try to actually check all of the balances and check that everything is working as intended.
我们就会尝试检查余额以及其它工作是否是我们所预期的那样
And if we don't see it, we're going to reject.
如果我们没看到触发，我们就返回 "reject"
And if there's a timeout, if it takes more than 200 seconds,
如果发生了超时，也就是如果它花费了超过 200 秒的时间
we're going to say okay, something went wrong, we're going to cancel it.
我们就会说，好吧，某些地方出错了，我们将撤销这次操作
And actually, I'm going to bump this up to 300 seconds, because I think 200 seconds is not going to be enough.
不过实际上，我会把它增加为 300 秒，因为我认为 200 秒的时间不太够
And depending on how quick the rink B test that is,
这具体取决于 Rinkeby 测试网的速度能有多快
you might have to bump this up even bigger. So just keep that in mind.
你可能会需要把它增加为更大的数值，请记住这一点